Profile

UX/UI designer with an passion for creating engaging, inclusive user experiences. Skilled in producing intuitive, creative solutions. Capable of working within a team and communicating design choices through storytelling.

Contact

- naomiweiler1@gmail.com
- (302) 668-5999
- website.com

Education

Careerfoundry 2021-2022

User Experience Design Immersion + Frontend Web Specialization

• Intensive project-based training program with a focus on user research, UX design, UI design, and frontend web development.

University of Delaware 2016-2020

B.S. Marketing & Management

Work History

Visual Designer 2021-2022

Terrain at Styer's

Designing botanical displays, conducting design consultations, assisting clientele, managing inventory

Digital Marketer 2021-2021

Diginuiti

Created marketing reports, found leads, developed and implemented marketing campaigns, and monitored SEO and google ad optimization

Customer Service Associate

2021-2021

Backcountry Outdoor Retailer

Stayed up to date on all product through clinic education, sold product, processed payment, fielding phone calls, messages, and emails, contacted/upkept client relationships

Decor Associate 2020-2021

Terrain at Styer's

Assisted clientele, answered phone calls and customer inquiries, sold product, kept inventory organized and clean, placed orders

Skills

User Research, User Interface, User-Centered Design, Wireframing, Personas, Style Guides, Usability, Responsive Grids

Tools

Figma
Sketch
HTML./CSS